(Leonard:)I know.
So what did you say?
(Leonard:)Thanks, sorry to bother you.
(Leonard:)But I said it like a badass.
(Penny:)All right, well,
can't you, like,
(Penny:)slip him some money
or something?
(Leonard:)Really? I've never done that
before. Does it work?
(Penny:)Do people like money...
is that what you're asking?
A... a lot of attitude
from the woman
(Leonard:)who thought MC squared
was a rapper.
(Penny:)Now, is that a smart thing
to say on a holiday
(Penny:)that's basically
national sex night?
(Leonard:)I'm sorry.
You're pretty, I'm stupid.
(Leonard:)Hello. Uh,
just checked again
for Hofstadter.
(Leonard:)Still gonna be an hour?
(clicks tongue)
I'm afraid so.
(Leonard:)Okay. Thanks.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Raj:)I think
(Leonard:)you may have dropped this?
(Raj:)Oh.
(Maitre d':)Did anybody lose a 20?
(Man:)I did.